for today let me begin by extending a
very happy welcome to all of our guests
present here to the launch of the second
edition of icici lombard corporate india
risk index press meet
my dear guest it is such a joy to
finally have our masks off and meet and
greet each other with a big smile on our
faces
we have overcome tremendous challenges
in the last two years and now as we see
the dawn of this new post-covet era it
is time to sit back and reflect to learn
from our past mistakes and work on a
better tomorrow
the biggest risk ladies and gentlemen is
not taking any risk
in a world that is constantly changing
the only strategy that is guaranteed to
fail is not taking risks said mark
zuckerberg and those words ring true
especially at present
so today we have amongst us industry
leaders who will be sharing their
thoughts with us on icici lombard
corporate indian risk index and i am
here to stitch the show together for you
now to shed light on icici lombard's
efforts in risk management and to set
the context for today
please allow me to invite our first
speaker for the day may i now invite mr
aloha girvan executive director icici
norwalk with a huge round of applause
everybody